I came here because
I was pissed about what you said.
Mm.
TAI-CHAN (AGE 22)
HAIRSTYLIST
So, you got a letter
on the first day here, right?
- And were you excited to get it?
- I was.
- [Assun] Yes, right?
- Mm-hmm.
ASSUN (30)
ENTREPRENEUR/HOSTESS
You can imagine how much it'd hurt
to write someone a letter
and never get a reply.
Mm.
[Ruru] At the very least,
you could have pulled Maririn aside
- to explain how you feel.
- [Assun] Exactly.
Mm.
No girl's gonna fall for a guy
who acts like that.
Mm.
What you did is something
that a "real man" would never do.
We've all been looking for a real man
in our relationships, not a boy.
RURU (26)
MODEL
We all came to this school
looking for that.
[Tai-chan] Mm.
So if this is the kind of guy you are,
none of us need you, okay?
Date other people if you want,
but be straight up about it.
[Tai-chan] Mm.
And Maririn has serious trauma
from past relationships.
MARIRIN (25)
BAR WORKER
- Which you found out today, right?
- Mm.
It's like you're not taking
Maririn's trauma seriously.
Yeah, I mean, I get it.
Um, it's true. You're right.
- I really messed up everything with you.
- [Maririn] Yeah.
And, you know, I'm just…
sorry.
- Anyone can say that. [laughs]
- Yep. Mm-hmm.
- [Ruru] This isn't to make you apologize.
- [Maririn] No, it's not.
- That's not why we're here.
- [Ruru] Right.
- What do they want from him? [sighs]
- [Megumi] I know.
I think it was good
that he apologized first, though.
[Nagano] You're right.
If you're not into her like that,
you should tell her.
- Mm.
- [Assun] But not talking to her?
And just, like…
leaving her hanging?
- And that's just not right.
- Mm.
I honestly think you're a piece trash.
- [Megumi] Wow.
- [Nagano] Did she need to go that far?
If you don't change,
if you can't act like a man,
- then no one is gonna love you.
- [Tai-chan] Mm.
It made me feel like
opening up to you was all for nothing.
It look a lot for me
to pour my heart out like that,
but now it seems like
you've just forgotten all of it.
You're shallow.
I realize now that
I didn't treat you right at all.
It was really pathetic of me.
- You mean it?
- [Tai-chan] Mm.
- [sniffles]
- [Awich] What?
- [Megumi] Aw, Tai-chan…
- [Nagano] Oh, come on, now.
- [Awich] What?
- [Megumi] Aw.
[Tai-chan sniffles]
[Megumi] Aw, Tai-chan's crying.
[cries softly]
I'll be straight up.
Everything's so messed up
right now. Mm-hmm.
She really poured her heart out
in that letter.
Mm… I just really messed it up.
Stupid.
It's pathetic.
So, tell me, what do you think about this?
I feel bad for him.
- [laughing] This time!
- Yeah, this time.
NAGANO
A STRONG RIVAL CAN BE A FRIEND
- [Ari] Here he is.
- [Ma-kun] Dude, he's here.
- [Ari] What's up?
- [Ma-kun] What's up?
- What's going on? What's wrong?
- What?
MA-KUN (28)
MMA FIGHTER
No, don't look so stressed.
What happened, man? What happened, dude?
- [Ari] Don't tell me you're sleepy.
- No, I'm not.
For real, what?
They just called me out.
What?
Assun, and Ruru
and Maririn.
So, wait, all three?
What do you mean?
So, yesterday,
she rewrote her letter to me.
- Maririn did, I mean.
- [Ma-kun] Okay.
LEO (25)
BAR OWNER
And after that,
I left things hanging all day
without saying anything.
I focused on Hikaru.
ARI (29)
RAPPER/MODEL
- [Ma-kun] Hmm…
- [Leo] Oh! Wow.
You probably should have talked to her.
Yeah.
You all know,
I've been saying from the start,
that I'm interested in Hikaru.
So you should be upfront with that too.
Don't act like you're into her,
if you're not, you know?
This time it was Maririn,
next time, it could be Hikaru.
And I don't even want to think about
what I would do if that happened.
Mm.
The girls are definitely
seeing things differently than we do.
- [Bou] Mm.
- They're not playing around.
- [Bou] Yeah, they're going deep.
- Uh-huh.
[Bou] They take it seriously.
[opening theme song playing]
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RAPPER FROM SAGAMIHARA
SPITTING LYRICS OF PURE LOVE
ARI
KAWASAKI'S IT-GIRL HOSTESS
OUT TO FIND A REAL MAN
HIKARU
KYOTO BAR OWNER
GOING ALL-IN FOR HIS WOMAN
NANIWA'S BARROOM BEAUTY
LOOKING FOR TRUE LOVE
MARIRIN
KURUME YANKII
WHO GREW UP BEHIND BARS
BO
EX-YAKUZA MMA FIGHTER
LOOKING FOR HIS RIDE-OR-DIE
MA-KUN
NAGOYA'S NO.1 HOSTESS
PUTS MEN IN THEIR PLACE
ASSUN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST
WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
AN HONEST MODEL
IN SEARCH OF LOVE
RURU
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
BADLY IN LOVE
MARINE ACADEMY
Morning.
- [Awich] Oh!
- [Nagano] Wow, no makeup.
[Megumi] She went bare-faced.
HIKARU (23)
HOSTESS
[Bou] This morning Hikaru
wasn't wearing any makeup. And like,
she looks the same
with nothing on her face.
She's cute, man.
BO (27)
COMMERCIAL PAINTER
So, I told her.
- [Nagano chuckles]
- [Megumi] Yeah!
- That's a nice smile.
- [Nagano] Good smile.
I guess I like no makeup.
Yeah, I was pretty taken by her.
It made me think
maybe it's time to get serious.
[laughs]
[sighs]
- [men] Morning.
- Hello.
- [Ari] Good morning.
- [Leo] Here they are.
- [Ruru] Morning.
- All right.
So, can I talk?
- [Leo] Yeah, sure.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
- Oh, wait.
- [Leo] What?
'Sup? Good morning.
- [all] Good morning.
- Hello.
So, something happened yesterday.
I didn't handle it well, at all.
Um, you know, I took the easy way out,
my response was lame.
I just wasn't honest
about how I felt, at all.
Of course, I told the guys what happened.
And I think,
that the girls all talked about it too.
But I wanted to be straight with everyone
today, and tell you all that I'm sorry.
Um… And believe me, I know that…
that actions,
they speak louder than words, so,
I'm gonna do better from here on out.
Don't give up on me.
- Thank you!
- All right.
[Assun] We're back on track.
- So, you're good now?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- [Assun laughs]
- Yo, apparently, he passed out last night.
Uh-huh. Like a baby.
- How the hell did you sleep?
- [all laughing]
- He passed out.
- [Ma-kun] No, you didn't sleep.
- [Leo and Bou] He didn't.
- [Ruru] Really?
[bell chiming]
BRING ON THE LOVE
[boy on PA] We have
a nice date planned for you today.
- [Ruru] Awesome. Love it.
- [Ari] Let's go!
- It'll be wild.
- [Hikaru] Yeah.
For today's date,
you'll enjoy Okinawa together
on a real activity date.
Oh, so cool.
The first woman who wins
- today's one-on-one competition…
- One-on-one?
will choose the man
she wants to take out on a date.
Please head out
and meet down at the beach.
- [Leo] What?
- [Tai-chan] Beach!
- [Ari] Dude, what is this?
- Wait, oh, it's tug-of-war.
- What?
- [Ma-kun] That's sick! Tug-of-war.
- [Assun] Tug-of-war?
- [Hikaru] What?
- [Leo] It'll be fun.
- [Ruru] They're making the girls do this?
- [Tai-chan] I guess so.
- [Ari] Whoa, a tournament? That's wild.
[Hikaru] It's one-on-one.
[Assun] Right,
and then the winner moves on.
What?
- Okay. Good luck, Maririn and Ruru.
- [Maririn] Yeah.
I'm so nervous.
- Aw, dang, don't be.
- I am.
- How're we more nervous than they are?
- You'll say "Go"?
- I'm more nervous.
- [Ruru] What?
- [Leo] Ready?
- [Ari] Let's go!
Ready? Fight!
- No, she's strong!
- I'm not losing.
- [Ari] Do it!
- [Leo] Go, go!
[Bou] That's right!
- It's a good match, don't give up.
- You're doing good.
- [Ari] They're not even moving.
- [Leo] Go!
Oh, no!
- Ow!
- What?
- No, not yet.
- Do you want a time-out?
- Call timeout?
- There's timeout?
- No timeouts, right?
- No timeouts.
- One pull it and she's got it.
- [Ma-kun] Pull it past and you win.
- Yeah, you got it.
- Winner!
1ST ROUND
WIN: MARIRIN, LOSS: RURU
You have insane grip strength.
- I do.
- You're crazy strong.
- Dude, don't try to call timeouts.
- [Assun] I know, totally!
For Ruru.
Yo, can you be a fair ref?
- You wanna go right here?
- Let's go!
2ND ROUND
LOSS: HIKARU, WIN: ASSUN
Bring it on. I'm gonna crush it.
Let's go, Hikaru! Crush it!
- [Hikaru] Killing it.
- [Ari] Let's go!
Listen, I play to win, dude.
I'm gonna win this.
Okay.
- Whoa!
- [Leo] Ready?
[Ruru] Assun is strong.
Ready? Fight!
[Ari] Let's go, Hikaru. Crush it!
- Whoa!
- Come on.
- Whoa.
- She's strong, man!
- [Leo] Winner!
- [Awich] It's so cool to be strong.
[Nagano] Yeah, it is.
2ND ROUND
LOSS: HIKARU, WIN: ASSUN
- Super strong. So strong.
- She wasn't even struggling.
[laughter]
- [Leo] Now it's the final.
- [Assun] Cool.
FINAL ROUND
MARIRIN VS. ASSUN
I'm definitely winning.
- [Leo] Yes!
- [Assun] Yup.
Yeah, I'm gonna go for it.
- [Ari] Go for it, yeah!
- [Ma-kun] Did you just wake up?
- [Leo] You ready?
- [Assun] Yes.
- [Ari] What's gonna happen?
- [Hikaru] Good luck, girls!
Ready? Fight!
- [Maririn yelps]
- [Leo] Are you kidding?
- She's super strong.
- [Leo] Sick!
- What's wrong?
- Genius.
- [Leo] She's not that strong.
- I know.
- [Hikaru] Oh, wait, this is crazy.
- Winner! Winner!
- [Awich] I like Assun. She's cool.
- [Maririn] She's really strong.
- [Ari] That's wassup!
- I won.
- [boy on PA] For the winner,
- So strong.
please choose the man
you'd like to take on your date.
Ma-kun, then.
- Okay, let's do it.
- [Assun chuckles]
- [Ari] Have fun!
- Let's go.
- Have a good time.
- Be careful.
- We will.
- Bye.
Have fun.
[Assun] Wow, the ocean, look!
- [Ma-kun] It's beautiful.
- This is amazing.
Three, two, one, go!
- Go!
- [man] Okay, have fun!
[upbeat music playing]
- You're so fast! [laughs]
- [Leo laughing]
- I'm faster!
- [Assun] That's crazy! [chuckles]
How are you so fast?
[Leo chuckling] Yay!
[Nagano] Aw, they're holding hands.
[Ma-kun] I think, uh,
that this is the very first time.
- [Assun] First time?
- That I'm touching you.
[Assun chuckles] Okay.
Do you ever hold hands?
- I don't.
- [chuckles]
Not really. Wait, do you?
No, not really.
- Not really?
- I would if we were dating.
- ATVs.
- Oh, ATVs.
On a normal day,
we don't offer these two-seater ATVs,
but we've prepared one here
especially for you.
- Wow.
- Yeah?
- Hold tight.
- Okay.
Oh! Whoa!
Whoa. We were talking yesterday
- about wanting to do this together, right?
- Yeah. This is cool.
- [Assun yelps] Whoa!
- [laughs]
Oh! [giggles]
[Megumi] This is bringing them closer.
It's fun too.
[upbeat music continues]
He was a really good ATV driver.
Honestly, if he hadn't been,
that would've been a turn-off.
- [Awich] Oh, I totally get that.
- [Megumi] That's exactly right.
[Assun] I'm not into guys
who are bad drivers.
If a guy can't drive properly,
I kind of feel like he'll end up
being bad at everything.
And when I held onto him,
his abs were rock solid.
[chuckling] I was like,
"His abs are insane."
I just kept touching them. [laughs]
Who touches that much? [laughs]
- [Nagano] I know, right?
- On the first date.
It's not like
they were attached at the hip.
[all laughing]
[boy on PA] The students
who didn't go on the date
will be at shikuwasa orchard helping out.
- [Ruru] Let's go.
- [Maririn] Let's pull weeds.
[laughs] You looked asleep.
- Who, me?
- Yes, you!
- When I was listening to you guys?
- I could be wrong, but you looked sleepy.
- No, once you started, I was awake.
- Really?
- You scared me.
- Wait, you were scared?
I guess getting dragged
- by three older girls would be scary.
- For real.
- You guys said a lot of tough things.
- Mm, said from love.
- [Tai-chan] I felt the love. Mm.
- [Maririn] Exactly.
- Wait, wait!
- What?
- Whoa, wait!
- Hey, no, wait!
- [yelps, yelps]
Ma'am! Ma'am!
- [Higa] A grasshopper?
- Help me, ma'am
I can't. [chuckles]
[Higa] They always find people
who hate them.
[Tai-chan] I'm legit scared.
- [Maririn] That was hilarious.
- It's not on my back, right?
Once that happens,
you can't stop feeling it. [laughs]
- [Tai-chan] No, I can't.
- [Maririn] You freaked out.
- [Nagano] Oh!
- [Megumi] Hikaru looks upset.
- [Nagano] Yeah.
- [laughing]
Bou, you love nature?
I don't love nature.
I'm just used to doing this.
[Ruru] Why? You do this back home?
- Well, I had that little gap.
- [Ruru] Oh, really?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, wait, they have this work?
- They do.
- For real?
- [laughs] Bou's already done weeding.
- [laughs]
[Ruru] That experience
can come in handy, I guess.
- Sometimes.
- [Ruru] Yeah.
[Megumi] Yeah, he's fast
because he has experience.
- The weather's so nice, it's so unfair.
- Yeah, for real.
- They're on a date.
- [chuckles] They're on a date.
- Leo, Leo. [laughing]
- Oh! Stop it.
- Stop it!
- [Nagano] They're having a good time.
- [Leo] This is an activity date.
- [Ruru] Yeah. This is a real activity.
- I can't think about what they're doing.
- [Ruru] They'll come back so happy.
- Totally. They're so easy to read.
- [laughs] Right? I can totally see it.
[Leo] Mm.
Yo! A jacuzzi!
And booze.
[chill music playing]
Whoa.
[grunts]
- [Nagano] Whoa!
- Can I join you?
- [Ma-kun] Yeah, come on in.
- [Megumi] Sexy.
- This is nice.
- Dang, this view is amazing.
- Yeah.
- I thought it'd be better in the dark…
- Me too, yeah.
- …but this is…
- It's cool this way too.
- It's better with the view.
Did that tattoo hurt? It did, right?
- Tattoos hurt.
- They hurt, right?
- Come on, you know.
- Yeah, I do.
[both laugh]
- Did you use numbing cream?
- I did.
[both laugh]
- I used numbing cream.
- You're not a real man.
I've never used it once.
Really? Respect.
- [Assun] When did you get your first?
- Oh, my first tattoo?
- I was… 17.
- Same.
Seventeen? Yes.
- We're so similar. [laughs]
- Mm, yeah.
[Assun] So, how does a relationship
level up?
- [Ma-kun] Don't know!
- [both laugh]
So right now,
we're still in the platonic stage.
- Right, uh--
- But--
- What's platonic?
- [laughs]
- Platonic love.
- What's that?
- It basically means it's pure.
- Oh, yeah, okay.
- Sure.
- Like, holding hands makes you happy.
Uh-huh. [laughing]
I get that.
People call you Ma-kun?
My ex called me Ma-kun.
Oh, so can I call you something else?
- Yeah. Like--
- What do you like?
Just Masaya.
- Just Masaya?
- Mm. Masaya.
That's good.
The only person who calls me Masaya
is my boss from the old organization.
And I really liked that guy,
that's why I stayed so long.
- Cheers, Masaya!
- To Masaya.
- Platonic Masaya.
- [laughs]
"Platonic Masaya."
The "call me by my name"?
That whole thing?
[Nagano] Yeah.
- "My boss from the organization…"
- [laughs]
That's wild.
- That sounds like a threat.
- [Awich laughs]
- It could be, no?
- And you suddenly get, that rush…
- [Nagano] Yeah.
- …like [gasps].
Oh, I know.
You're mistaking an organization rush
for a romantic one.
[laughing]
"His boss from the organization."
An org-rush and a romantic rush
aren't the same.
- No, exactly. They're completely opposite.
- Worlds apart.
- Do you have a sec?
- Sure.
- Tai-chan.
- Let's go.
- [Hikaru] Do you need cigarettes?
- I have some.
[sighs] Come on.
[Bou] Dude, I don't get girls.
- [Leo] Me neither.
- Hmm.
[Megumi] Oh.
Ari is…
- [Leo] You're so obvious.
- What?
I don't care.
[Megumi] He's obviously annoyed.
[Nagano] He's dying.
Do you know why I asked you out here?
- We went to the orchard, right?
- Mm.
When we were there,
you barely talked to me.
Mm.
Yeah, so, about that…
- I did have reasons.
- Mm.
So, Ari is interested…
Mm-hmm.
…in you, Hikaru.
- Me and Bou, too.
- Mm.
- We all want to get to know you.
And so, it just felt weird,
cutting into their time with you.
So you hung back?
- Okay, honestly?
- Mm.
And I swear I'm not trying
to make excuses, but my head is just,
it's all over the place today.
'Cause, yesterday.
Are you serious?
What the hell?
This is so frustrating.
Come on, hurry up!
[Bou] There he goes.
Hikaru and Taisei here?
- They went out for a smoke.
- [Ari tuts] Okay, thanks.
- Bye.
- Yeah.
[groans in frustration]
This sucks.
For real. Where did they go?
You're kidding me.
I have no clue how to get around here.
- [laughing]
- [Megumi] I can't help you there.
- He's having a hard time.
- That one's all you, Ari.
I have to say, this morning,
you know,
when you spoke in front of the class?
I really felt your sense of integrity.
- Hmm.
- And I thought, "Wow, he's changed."
So, I mean,
you've been, like…
- Mm.
- …just really on my mind.
Mm.
- And I'm gonna tell Maririn that.
- What?
That Hikaru is…
the only girl I want to see.
[Megumi] Aw.
What is that? [laughing]
- What is that face?
- "Yeah?"
That grin, yeah.
Like they said,
"Just like that, hold there!"
[laughs]
I'm gonna be sick.
Not here!
- [Awich] He's still looking for them?
- [Nagano] Yeah.
Seriously, what?
There's nobody. Is this a deserted island?
Like, where did they go?
[Megumi] It's a school.
This shouldn't be hard.
How I feel…
hasn't changed.
That's me.
[Ari] What are you doing?
What?
[Ari] What gives?
It's been like five hours!
- [Hikaru] It hasn't been that long.
- I'm crashing this.
- [Hikaru laughs]
- Let's talk.
Okay.
- [Ari] Busy?
- All right.
- Hello.
- Hi!
- Oh, it's nice to meet you, hi!
- Nice, yeah.
I'm Ari.
So, before you said
you weren't interested in anyone, right?
- Mm.
- Still true?
For better or for worse,
I think I've gotten
a little too comfortable around you.
So wait, what does that mean?
It's not like I'm keeping you as a backup.
- I'm really not…
- Doesn't look that way.
…but I'm worried that's how it looks.
But I do worry, so…
But you're still open to considering me,
is that right?
Right.
But I'm seriously thinking about marriage,
so I'm being careful.
Mm, I'm not in love yet.
[Ari] Hmm.
- [Nagano] Hmm, really?
- [Megumi] Oh.
[Leo] I think they're having
a really good date.
[Ruru] It really seems like
they're moving forward.
I bet they kissed.
- [Ari] Really?
- Hope they did.
- [Hikaru] Oh, they're back! Come in!
- We're back!
- [squeals, laughs]
- [Leo] Hey, hey.
[Ma-kun] We're back. What's up?
Oh, nice! Dude, I want to eat too.
- Yeah, I'm hungry.
- [Bou] They did it.
- [Assun] It smells so good.
- [Ma-kun] Good.
- [Assun] Don't crowd us, okay?
- [Maririn] Eat it.
[Ma-kun] It's fine.
- [Hikaru] Did you kiss?
- [both] We didn't.
- Wait, they didn't?
- No way.
Hey, but wait, is that… is that true?
- We didn't. No.
- It's true, right?
- Of course we didn't.
- [Hikaru] Of course you didn't?
- Because our relationship is platonic.
- Platonic.
- Hey do you know what that word means?
- Don't know.
- What's platonic?
- He doesn't know it.
It means pure.
It means we're having a pure relationship.
It's really moving forward.
It's "Badly in Love," right?
[Leo] It's annoying that
you're acting so confident now.
- We were bored, so we came to find you.
- [Bou] Sorry to disturb.
When we were talking to you ladies,
- you shared about domestic violence.
- [Maririn] Right.
- I didn't get what you meant.
- [Maririn] What part?
I guess it's like, the woman gets mad,
but the man gets more in a rage.
[Maririn] Mm-hmm.
But I just don't understand…
why it turns violent.
I was always told that
it was because I didn't listen.
Mm, I was told the same thing.
- So he shut me up.
- I'll say this now, though I know
it makes me look bad,
but when I was young,
- I was cheated on.
- [both] Mm.
And I lost it.
I went blank, and I hit her.
But I don't think I'd…
that I'd ever do it for no reason.
[Ruru] Mm.
I could never hit a woman.
- [Ruru] Mm.
- That's impossible.
Well, you know,
this might just be an excuse,
but I think it was because
I was still young.
- I'd never do that now.
- Mm.
So you hit her and then you realized it?
- Yeah, I knew it was wrong.
- [Maririn] Really?
Mm, I was so frustrated the whole time.
So, then I thought I had to go
and find the guy, and I found him.
- That scared her.
- [Megumi] Yeah, I agree.
She got really scared right there.
But I think it might have been scary
if he'd kept it to himself.
- Right. Hmm.
- That's true.
I do think it was good
that he told them about it.
It really seems like the girls
are the ones in charge.
- In this season, yes.
- [Nagano] In this season.
- The guys are a little bit scared.
- Yes.
- Mm
- Listen, Leo just said "ladies."
- Yes. "Talking with you ladies." [laughs]
- [Nagano] "With you ladies."
- Leo looks like a member of Skapara.
- [laughing]
That looks like a mash-up
of some of the Skapara members.
- [Megumi] He does. I see that.
- [Nagano] Like a blend of all of them.
- [bell chiming]
- [Hikaru] I've heard of it.
MARINE ACADEMY
LOVE
[Ari] To know if you thought it was cool.
I like it.
[boy on PA] Today, we have
an extracurricular activity.
You'll experience traditional
- Okinawan Mouashibi.
- [Awich] What?
This will deepen your bonds
with each other.
- What is it?
- "Mouashibi"?
- What's that?
- [Bou] What?
- Is it okay to do Mouashibi?
- [Nagano] Why? What's Mouashibi?
Is it okay to do Mouashibi?
[boy on PA] Mouashibi is a tradition
passed down through the ages in Okinawa.
This is where young people
would enjoy dancing and singing together,
and hope to find the one they'll marry.
- This is so Okinawa!
- That's amazing.
- Wow, cool. Shiku-wassup!
- Wow.
[Ari] It's Taiko no Tatsujin.
That's awesome.
- [Assun] Whoa.
- [Ma-kun] What?
- [Ari] Sick!
- [traditional music playing]
[Ari] Cool, right?
[Ma-kun] Incredible.
So cool!
- [cheering]
- So great!
Wassup, man!
Whoo!
You guys, that was cool.
- That was crazy!
- Yeah.
- [Bou] Okay, lunch.
- [Ma-kun] Great.
- [Hikaru] What's in there?
- [Ma-kun] Look at this.
- [Assun] Wait, this is crazy.
- [Bou] Whoa.
- [Ruru] Looks delicious.
- [Ari laughing] What? No way!
Should we? All right. One…
two, three…
[all] Wassup!
- [laughter]
- [all] Let's eat.
Dig in.
- Yeah, it's nice.
- So sick! Kakuni.
- [Bou] Good.
- Off the chain, right?
- [Assun] I'm starving.
- Whoa!
[Ari] Crazy, right?
[upbeat music playing]
[Nagano] Oh! What?
- [Awich] A newcomer.
- [Megumi] Mm.
Oh!
- [Ruru] Whoa. Who's there?
- [Bou] What?
- [giggles]
- [Ma-kun] Wassup!
- Wassup, bro!
- [woman] Hello.
- Wassup, wassup!
- [Bou] Hey.
I'm Hazuki, transfer student.
But you can call me Ha-chan. Hi.
- [Ma-kun] Nice to meet you.
- [Tai-chan] Good to meet you.
- [Leo] Welcome.
- [Hikaru] Welcome.
[Ma-kun] Welcome.
HAZUKI ABE
AKA HA-CHAN (27)
I'm Hazuki, I'm 27.
I'm from Miyagi Prefecture.
They call me Ha-chan.
I actually work as a kickboxing trainer.
- I started kickboxing for real at 19.
- [Awich] Awesome.
Compared to most people,
yeah, I think I've definitely
been through hell in my life.
- [Nagano] Oh.
- I was in a center, a children's home.
All of my exes have been arrested,
that's usually why
we'd end up breaking up.
They were arrested for drugs or fraud.
So they'd end up in jail
for three or four years at time.
I want someone who won't get arrested.
It's like a police video.
- I see it.
- [Nagano] With "drugs" and "fraud" there.
DRUGS FRAUD
- It's like a police poster.
- [Megumi] It's a "Just say no" ad.
I want a fair person
with a determined mind.
I don't like when guys look like
a yankii, but really aren't.
I haven't been treated like a woman
for a while, so I forget. [giggles]
So I want a guy to help me remember.
[chuckles]
- Welcome. Wassup?
- [laughs]
- Oh, sorry.
- All good.
Oh, wow. [laughs]
This is intense.
- "Intense" is crazy.
- [Ha-chan] Because you look awesome.
- Are we intense?
- Who has the most intense vibes?
- I don't know.
- You don't?
Well, you.
You look like you used to be a druggie.
- [laughter]
- [Megumi] Choose your words.
- [Ha-chan] Sorry.
- [Ruru] Hey.
- [Megumi] He's not laughing.
- [Nagano] Oh, wow, he didn't laugh?
So now you've seen us,
tell us which guy is your type.
Oh, my type?
I like his face.
- [laughter]
- [Leo] Oh!
- Why, thank you. Thanks.
- I like a genuinely strong guy.
I hate it when guys think they're tough
because they have tattoos,
but really, they're just wimps.
I want a guy who stands up for himself.
That's my type.
- [Megumi] Huh?
- [Nagano] What happened?
- What's going on?
- Gotta sit next to the girl you're into.
That's right.
Let's introduce ourselves.
- [Ha-chan] Yes, please.
- [Bou] Yeah.
- I'm Tai-chan, I'm 22.
- Oh, cool.
Tokyo is home.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
- [Ha-chan] What do you do?
- I do hair.
- Oh. Good to meet you.
- [Tai-chan] Yeah, you too.
[Ruru] Welcome.
- That's in right now.
- Did you see that?
- It's totally a thing.
- [Ari] This is annoying.
- [Leo] Never done it.
- But it has changed.
- [Maririn] Myers-Briggs.
- [Ha-chan] What was it? [sighs]
- [Bou] Did he leave?
- [Leo] He did.
- [Ha-chan] Okay.
- [Maririn] He's upset?
- What's wrong?
- He's really upset.
- [Bou] Hitting the bathroom.
- [Ruru] What?
- He left? [laughs]
- [Assun] He left.
- Is that like him?
- [Ma-kun] He's feeling bad.
[Hikaru] You okay?
- You pissed?
- Yeah, I'm so pissed.
- I mean, I--
- Yeah, I saw your face, man.
- Yeah?
- Uh-huh.
She says I look like I do drugs?
What's wrong with her?
And look, I mean, no one even
comes close to you, Hikaru.
No matter who shows up,
all of them are just duds anyway.
It just made me feel shitty.
Some girl I don't know
calling me a damn druggie.
Yeah, read the room.
A druggie? Is that really wassup? Hell no.
Nah, no wassup.
[laughing] I don't know
what "wassup" means.
- [laughing]
- [Nagano] What's "wassup"?
I don't know what's happening!
- "Is that really wassup?"
- [Nagano] So, "Is that wassup?"
- I wonder how she'll act now.
- Yeah.
[Ha-chan] What's your story, Bou?
How would you describe yourself?
Um, I guess I'd call myself a joker.
In one word.
- Always.
- I bet we're the same age.
- Born in '98?
- Yes, sir.
I'm surprised
there's someone else my age here.
- '98, year of the tiger?
- Year of the tiger.
- Same, same. Yeah.
- [laughs]
- You were arrested?
- For assault and extortion.
Just assault and extortion, huh?
- Yeah, and drugs.
- Hmm.
- What kind of drugs? Meth?
- Uh, yeah.
Right. Okay, show me, then.
- No, I smoked it.
- Oh, yeah? Oh.
[bell chiming]
[boy on PA] Today, we have
the welcome party for the new student,
and you can drink.
- [Ma-kun] Okay, okay.
- [Ha-chan] Yay!
So what kind of things
do you want to know about us?
Tell me everything?
I'm still mixing you guys up.
- I am.
- Should we say our names?
Say your names? Yes, please.
Wait, we did that already. At lunch.
- [Ma-kun] If you forget our names, ask.
- [Assun] It's hard to remember everyone.
- Cheers to us!
- [all cheer]
[Leo] Hey!
[Nagano] It seems like
she's not really accepted yet, right?
[Megumi] Right.
[Ha-chan] I feel like
you're all really bonded.
- Well, I mean, honestly? For real, though?
- [Ha-chan] Mm-hmm.
I can't accept
a transfer student so easily.
Because this all happened fast.
So, I've been living in Tokyo
since I moved there at 20,
and the only people I call my good friends
are from back home.
- [Ha-chan] I see.
- So, I'm not the type to trust easily.
Once we have shared history
and shared lives,
then I usually start to feel like
we can be friends.
I wanted to tell you this in person,
because I don't want to talk
about you behind your back.
I just wanted to be really clear
that I don't trust people easily.
[Megumi] They're hard on the new girl.
[Ruru] Actually,
I want to talk to you alone.
[Ha-chan] Oh, okay.
- I'm feeling confrontational right now.
- Mm.
I can't handle having someone here
who I don't see as one of us.
I get it, but there's no point
in saying that.
- I know there's no point.
- Yeah.
But it's gonna take time
for me to see you as family, Hazuki.
If you can't, you can't.
It's not about whether you can or not.
You don't have the right attitude.
I expect you to say, "But I want
to be family, so I'll work at it."
- That's what I want.
- That's what you wanted.
But that's hard.
I can't just start liking someone
because they ask me to.
I mean, it's fine if you can't do it.
And I don't see someone as family
unless I feel they really are, either.
Oh, see, it's really the same way for you.
You want to know the person first too.
I thought I'd try to be mature
and tell you this.
That's why I wanted to talk.
I can really tell that
you really want to do the right thing.
- [Ruru] Mm.
- Mm.
Today was the first day we met,
and this is my first one-on-one
- with, uh, one of the girls.
- Mm-hmm.
I think we might be the same.
- I know! And I fight with people like me!
- [laughing]
For real, I told them, I never get along
with people who are like me.
I don't.
Yeah, it's pretty hard being
a transfer student.
- [Megumi] Yeah, apparently.
- [Awich] But she faced it well.
[Ha-chan] When I talked with Ma-kun,
he said I should apologize to Ari
for saying that he looked like a druggie,
and he's right.
So, I wanted to go
and find Ari to apologize.
[door opens]
- Ari, you have a sec?
- [Ari] Who, me?
[Ha-chan] Yeah.
- There's something I want to talk about.
- Oh, yeah?
So, you know that
I really got thrown into things today.
Mm-hmm.
And so when you
were sitting next to me at lunch,
- I said, "You look like a druggie."
- Ah.
And I said it as a joke.
It really was meant as just a joke.
- Huh. Mm.
- I wasn't serious, at all.
And I wanted to apologize.
Oh, okay.
- I wanted to say that.
- Oh, is that it?
So, my ex was a druggie,
and, um, he ended up
choking and suffocating me.
Honestly, I have a lot of trauma from that
- and I shouldn't pass judgment onto you.
- Yeah.
So, in the rap scene, right?
It's a common thing.
Super common, really. It's everywhere.
Lots of druggies.
One of my old rapper friends did drugs.
That guy was a real addict,
and he had a ton of overdoses,
and he was wanted by the police.
One time, we had a meeting
before a concert, and the cops came.
They took him away,
and they made me take a urine test.
Mm-hmm.
They took me
to the police station, interrogated me,
and, oh, man, the concert was canceled.
That happened a lot.
And I was like,
"What's the point of this?", right?
- Right, when you're working so hard.
- He's messing things up for his friends.
So I've really hated drugs,
- ever since then.
- You hate them.
And a lot of my work
comes from the city government,
so I make sure not to do that stuff.
I don't even go to places
where it's happening.
- Oh, I feel really bad now. [sighs]
- So…
- No, no, it's okay.
- Uh-huh.
- How'd you know if I hadn't told you?
- Right.
And you apologized,
so I won't hold it against you.
I just really… I wanted you
to understand that I went through that.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- I really am.
- [Megumi] Good apology.
- [Awich] Yeah.
You've changed my impression of rappers.
- He changed her impression of rappers.
- Good to hear.
- [laughing]
- [Nagano laughs] "Good to hear."
- That's good to hear, but…
- Yeah.
Is it true that rappers
are associated with drugs?
Yeah, yeah. That's true.
Back in the '80s, when hip-hop
was really just starting to take off…
[Megumi] Mm-hmm.
- …drugs were already a major problem.
- [both] Mm.
And there was a lot violence too.
Racial and economic discrimination
was still prevalent
in a lot of the United States,
so, as a way to escape from all that,
rap developed as
an artistic medium of expression.
It was a way of escaping
what was happening in life.
And performers would rap
about their experiences.
[both] Mm.
So because they were saved by the music…
- [Megumi] Right.
- …they tended to think it was good,
that whole kind of attitude around it,
and um, it still remains.
- [Megumi] Mm.
- Yeah, I see.
So, now that we have Ha-chan too,
how will they--
- You said Ha-chan, I heard "antisocial".
- [laughing]
I thought,
"Okay, that's where we are now."
- It's not.
- See, they're not all like that.
- Antisocial people.
- Not antisocial.
- We don't know.
- Excuse me,
- but even at Netflix, that's not allowed.
- I'm sorry.
- [Assun] Oh!
- [Leo] Whoa! Nice!
- No, no--
- Get it.
One more time. That's mine.
- [Leo] Go.
- [Hikaru] Yeah, I'm no match for you, sis.
- No, you can't.
- Can I stand here?
- No, please!
- All right?
- Wait.
- Stop flirting.
- [Awich] Whoa.
- [Megumi] Getting close. Wow.
She's really cute.
When she came over to me, like that,
it's not "like" anymore. It's "love."
She totally stole my heart.
Today, and tomorrow too.
I'm Ruru crazy.
Cheers!
[imperceptible]
- [Awich] Oh, that's nice.
- [Nagano] Wow, that's nice! For rivals.
[Megumi] He's a hairstylist, you know.
- Thank you, Taisei.
- [Tai-chan] You got it.
- [Nagano] He's refreshing.
- [Megumi] He looks good when working.
- [Nagano] Yeah!
- [Megumi] Mm.
[Ari] I didn't expect this hairstylist
with so many tattoos.
- [Ma-kun] Me neither.
- [Ari] Yeah.
[Leo] I thought he was a rapper.
- Really? "You did?"
- [Leo] Yeah, I thought, "Really? Is he?"
Same, I thought,
"Why are there so many rappers?"
- Rapper, yakuza, rapper.
- [Ari] Really?
And that was it.
- You're done.
- [Ma-kun] Thank you.
- [Ari] True! That's cool.
- [Ma-kun] I'm different now.
[Ari] Yo, yo, yow!
[bell chiming]
- [boy on PA] A new student is coming.
- Again?
- [Ha-chan] Wait, what?
- [Hikaru] Wait. Shh!
What? For real?
Everyone, please go welcome them
in the classroom.
- [Hikaru] What?
- [Assun] Now?
[Maririn] A guy?
- Could it be another guy?
- Woo-hoo!
- [laughing]
- [whooping excitedly]
- [Ha-chan laughing] She's crazy.
[rap music playing]
- [Awich] It's a guy.
- [Nagano] Whoa, look at this guy!
Uh-oh, he looks handsome.
[music continues]
BADLY IN LOVE
MARINE ACADEMY
[imperceptible]
[Awich] What was that?
- What reaction was that?
- [Megumi] Oh, she thinks he's hot.
[Ruru] Oh.
Hello.
Uh, I'm Kazuma Shioda.
Thank you.
[dramatic music playing]
People call me Kazu-kun.
KAZUMA SHIODA
AKA KAZU-KUN (29)
I run a… a host club.
I've been living alone all my life
and I'd say violence,
uh, it's basically all around me.
Women?
Always like me.
How many women?
Don't remember.
You don't remember how many times
you've eaten meat, right?
I'm hot.
I have money.
I'm funny.
And I'm kind.
I like my face, yeah. Mm.
When I wake up, I'm glad to be me.
It's good to be me. [laughs]
- Oh, man, we've got a wild one!
- Okay, thank you.
He's speaks his mind.
Ruru was reacting so much.
- See that?
- [Megumi] Right.
[Nagano] Do you all really act
like this? [laughs]
Like an old lady watching a Korean star?
[mockingly] "Oh, what do I do?
A cute boy is here."
It's fine when she's young,
but you can imagine
what she'll be like when she's older.
- I bet she'll be obsessed with Korea!
- [both laughing]
But isn't she being too obvious?
Do they know each other?
I'm 29 years old…
KAZU-KUN (29)
TOKYO - HOST CLUB OWNER
…from Toyama Prefecture.
And I'm here for love,
so, I won't be friends with the guys.
So, girls, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
- [Ari] Then go home. Go home.
'Cause you don't have a room, chump. What?
You don't want friends?
- I don't.
- [Ari] You don't have a room, bitch.
- What're you gonna do? You brat.
- Sit down.
Huh? What?
- I said you don't have a room, punk. Hey.
Are you a freakin' punk? Huh?
- [Megumi] Ari's never like this.
- [Nagano] Yeah.
- [Ari] Piece of crap.
- [Nagano] He's the feel-good guy.
[bell chiming]
[boy on PA] Attention, boys.
To welcome the new student,
please work together
to make him a welcome dinner.
There's no way I'm doing that.
You'll make your own dinner,
because you don't have any friends.
Clear?
You were told, so make it.
Only if I agree, right? I didn't agree.
You said you don't want to make friends.
- [Kazu-kun] Mm.
- Huh?
- So why would I do that?
- Just do what you're told.
You make it. Yeah?
- You were told to.
- [Bou] You!
The hell?
Hey!
- [Megumi] Uh-oh.
- Make your own dinner.
[Nagano] Whoa!
You make it.
- [Megumi] Oh, no. Oh, my.
- [Nagano] Here they go.
[dramatic music playing]
[Ma-kun] Go outside. Go outside.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, fine. Chill a sec.
[Bou] Sorry.
[Ma-kun] You okay?
- Are you okay?
- I went flying.
[Bou clears throat]